{
    "id": "b81dc90eb26242d58e6ea6286c043f66",
    "title": "Noun + Preposition Combinations",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We had little hope …………………. success nonetheless, we decided to perform the operation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e839f25c0b954530a1e3030434cbbc4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cash-for-vote scandal did a lot of harm …………………… his reputation as a conscientious politician.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "142311141495407fb2b63078df68996f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have to find a substitute ……………………… it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48bd9fef8c7449be98b9e2b28d84c48c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should deem it as an attack ……………………… our right to privacy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6ef86c48b3d40d9b1f1a6643302cb20"
        },
        {
            "question": "In many cities the cost …………………… living is pretty high.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7e1071ebfa0c483bb60b96c0188f6f41"
        },
        {
            "question": "We would like to see a big increase ………………….. productivity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48c7932516834d7895b05a8fa5c95d81"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no interest ……………………… politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f3f1907eb32407ab52639ae7eb06a03"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no faith ………………… her capabilities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2491c88267646608a814f0274001268"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have heard that the government is planning to raise the tax …………………… automobiles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "394900074936400b877e2178eea27597"
        },
        {
            "question": "I admire their way ………………… doing things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8307cac0646b4c5f942668986fd9b36f"
        }
    ]
}